lookpdf.com 2009-03-11

# Privacy Policy LooKPDF.com - Search Portable Document Format Files for FREE

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We may also track IP addresses for purposes of enrollment and/or subscription.

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

A cookie is a data file that certain websites write to your PC/Computer when you visit such sites or blog. A cookie file can contains information, such as a user identification code, that the site uses to maintain a personalized look and feel on the pages you have visited. LookPDF uses cookies solely to maintain user access levels throughout the web site. This data is used on an anonymous basis and we do not correlate this information with personal data of any user. 

This site contains links to other sites. LookPDF is not responsible for the privacy practices of such Web sites. LookPDF is not responsible for any content on any linked sites or for any goods or services available from them.

LookPDF works hard to ensure that the information contained on our web pages is accurate, relevant and of the high quality that our visitors have come to expect.

We are aware of software that exists which will create external links from our content to what they consider to be related material, which other companies have paid to have shown. We are not responsible for the quality of this software or the nature of the material that it links to

We emphasize that we are strictly against this form of unmoderated and unregulated link advertising and strictly prohibit its use within our site content.

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies like Google (www.google.com/adsense), etc. that place ads on our web site. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies, with the help of cookies, may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policy of each those websites. Privacy Policy of Google is available at <http://www.google.com/privacy.html> .While your individual information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use aggregated anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners. 

The materials appearing on LookPDF's web site could include technical, typographical, photographic or URL download errors. If you feel the PDF files contains copyrighted material, you can send message to info@lookpdf.com and we will detele it soon. LookPDF does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. LookPDF may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. LookPDF make any commitment to update the materials reguraly.
